Bauchwitz, Kurt (Roy C. Bates); Papers ger011
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Correspondence Files, 1914-1987; 2; 1 Digital Files 429 file folders
  - Correspondence regarding Literary Topics, 1941-1976; 2.3; 125 file folders
    - Exposition Press (Edward Uhlan), 1962; 1974-1976 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 79)
      6 letters from, 2 letters to; publisher's advertisements.
    - Faber and Faber Ltd., 1960 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 80)
    - Finkelstein, Maurice, 1953 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 81)
      3 letters from, 3 letters to; typescript: R.C.B. "On the psychology of law-business". Typescript with h. corr. 7p.
    - Forum (Columbia University), 1968 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 82)
    - Friedlander, Harold, 1946; 1953 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 83)
      4 letters to.
    - Fromm, Leni (WGBH). Notes of a telephone conversation, 1972 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 84)
    - Fujita, Masayrki, 1977 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 85)
    - Funk & Wagnalls Company (Unicorn Press Publishers), 1947 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 86)
      2 letters from, 1 letter to; encyclopedia pages.
    - Furioso (Carlton College), 1951-1952 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 87)
      4 letters from, 2 letters to.
    - Gentry, 1951-1952 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 88)
    - Gittings, Theodore B. (Western Union Telegraph Company), 1949 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 89)
    - Giury, Patrick, 1971-1972 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 90)
      11 letters from, 10 letters to.
    - Gutmann, Rudolph J., 1950 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 91)
    - Harding, Douglas. Correspondence, 1960-1971; 2.3.45 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 92-96)
      41 letters from, 66 letters to, 6 related letters; 2 drawings, 1 photograph; offprints; notes from R.C.B.
      - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 4 (2.3.45-Harding, Douglas. Correspondence), Folder 92)
      - Correspondence, 1961-1971 (Box 4 (2.3.45-Harding, Douglas. Correspondence), Folder 93)
      - 2 pencil drawings (self-portraits presumably from Harding), 1 photograph (Box 4 (2.3.45-Harding, Douglas. Correspondence), Folder 94)
      - Typescripts and reprints of articles by Harding, Undated (Box 4 (2.3.45-Harding, Douglas. Correspondence), Folder 95)
        11 items
      - Notes by Bates pertaining to Harding and his writings, ca. 40p (Box 4 (2.3.45-Harding, Douglas. Correspondence), Folder 96)
    - Harding, M. Esther, 1950 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 97)
      1 letter from, 4 letters to.
    - Harper & Brothers, 1960 (Box 4 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 98)
    - Harper's Bazaar, 1951 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 1)
    - Henderson, Harold G., 1969 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 2)
    - Hochland, 1951 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 3)
    - Horch, Franz J., 1942 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 4)
    - Hunt, Clinton, 1972 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 5)
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group (Gerald Yorke), 1961 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 6)
      4 letters from, 4 letters to.
    - Johnson, Pamela H. (Lady Snow), 1970 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 7)
    - Joseph, Nannine, 1946 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 8)
    - Kane, Katherine D., 1965 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 9)
      3 letters from, 2 letters to; 3 cl.
    - "The Last Word", 1957 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 10)
      2 cards from, 2 letters to; 3 cl.
    - Lawson, Rev. Robert W., 1971 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 11)
    - LeCoq, Elinor von, 1940 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 12)
    - Life, 1962; 1967 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 13)
      2 letters from, 2 letters to; 2 cl.
    - Lucey, Stuart & Betty, 1950 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 14)
    - MacCampbell, Donald, 1967 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 15)
      1 letter to; 1 cl.; notes.
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1942 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 16)
    - The MacMillan Company Publishers, 1945 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 17)
    - Margolius, Hans, 1963 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 18)
    - Martini, Fritz, 1958-1963 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 19)
      11 letters from, 15 letters to, 5 related letters.
    - McCullers, Carson, 1951 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 20)
    - McMurtie, Douglas C, 1942 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 21)
    - Mead, Daniel S., Literary Agent, 1950 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 22)
      1 letter from, 2 letters to; advertisement.
    - Mehring, Walter, 1952 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 23)
    - Merkur (Hans Paeschke, Editor), Undated (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 24)
      notes; cl. Draft of 1 letter to.
    - The Middle Way (The Buddhist Society, London), 1967-1968 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 25)
      2 letters from, 6 letters to; Manuscript submission by R.C.B. "Question Marks". Typescript cc. 6p.; Photocopy of published selections.
    - The Milton Record - Transcript, 1967 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 26)
      2 letters to; notes; 4 cl. (incl. "Letter to the Editor" by R.C.B.).
    - Mode, Heinz and Therese, 1967-1971 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 27)
      23 letters, cards from, 22 letters to, 3 related letters.
    - Moreno, Jacob Levy, 1941 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 28)
      1 letter to, 1 related letter.
    - Morris, Claremont R., 1947 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 29)
    - The National Five Arts Award, Inc., 1949-1956 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 30)
      6 letters, cards pertaining to programs sponsored by The National Five Arts Award, Inc.
    - Neue Schweizer Rundschau, 1951-1953 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 31)
      4 letters from, 6 letters to; manuscript submissions by R.C.B.: 19 poems (2 c.), "Einsätze". 28p.
    - New York Times, 1943-1971 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 32)
      6 letters, cards from, 9 letters to; notes; 6 cl., incl. copies of 2 "Letters to the Editor" authored by R.C.B.
    - New Yorker, 1946 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 33)
    - Newsweek, 1966 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 34)
    - Niebuhr, Reinhold, 1956; 1966 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 35)
      2 letters from, 2 letters to; 1 cl.
    - Norden, Ruth & Heinz, 1947 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 36)
    - Northrup, Filmer S., 1948 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 37)
    - Nymphenburger Verlagshandlung (Martin Gregor-Dellin; Hansjörg Graf), 1965-1966 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 38)
      9 letters from, 14 letters to, 3 related letters; notes.
    - Pekrun, Richard, 1934-1935 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 39)
      2 postcards from, 2 letters to; typescripts of 2 poems by Bates.
    - Philosophical Library, 1958 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 40)
      1 letter to, 1 letter from.
    - PHP Institute (Ken Iwai, Managing Editor), 1969-1973 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 41)
      27 letters from, 11 letters to; notes; cl.
    - PHP Institute, Undated; 17 items (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 42)
      Notes ca. 30p.; cl., brochures.
    - Piscator, Erwin, 1950 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 43)
    - Popovici, Anton (Europäischer Verlag). Correspondence (with Barbara Bates), 1974-1976 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 44)
      4 letters from, 16 letters to, 6 related letters; signed contract between Barbara Bates, Harry Zohn and Popovici dated February 22/March 3, 1975.
    - Reader's Digest, 1945-1971 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 45)
      1 letter from, 5 letters to; manuscripts submitted by R.C.B. for publication: "Introducing the Index". 7p.; "Question Marks". 3p.; Untitled. 3p.
    - Renick, Helen Prokoff (Elena Proklova), 1967-1972 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 46)
      7 letters, cards, notes from, 1 letter to; 6 cl.
    - Riwkin, J., 1946-1947 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 47)
      2 letters from, 6 letters to.
    - Rosenberg, Karl, 1941 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 48)
      1 letter to; poem text.
    - Rukser, Udo (Deutsche Blätter), 1944-1964 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 49)
    - Russell, Lord, 1951 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 50)
    - Saturday Evening Post - poem manuscript "Prayer", Undated (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 51)
    - Saturday Review of Literature (Norman Cousins, Harrison Smith, John G. Fuller), 1945-1969 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 52)
      16 letters from, 46 letters to; manuscripts submitted by R.C.B. for publication: poems; "Cloud Cuckoo Town Library". Typescript 5p.; "SRL Advertising Campaign". Multiple copies. 4p. ea. Notes. Autograph ca. 5p.
    - Scala, 1967 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 53)
    - Schoenberner, Franz, 1965 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 54)
    - Schweizerische Monatsschrift, 1951 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 55)
    - Selye, Hans, 1957 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 56)
      1 letter from, 2 letters to; notes; 1 cl.
    - Shapiro, Arthur, 1958-1968; 1970 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 57)
      10 letters from, 13 letters to, 1 related letter; manuscript by R.C.B. "Dreamed QM". Typescript cc. 4p.
    - Shapiro, Arthur, Undated; 9 items (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 58)
      Reprints and articles.
    - Simpson, Joseph, 1966-1967 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 59)
      3 letters from, 5 letters to; 1 cl.
    - Smith, Huston, 1969 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 60)
      1 letter from, 4 letters to; 1 reprint.
    - Sperber, Manes, 1949-1951 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 61)
      2 letters from, 4 letters to; notes; 1 cl.
    - Die Tat (Erwin Jaeckle), 1970 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 62)
    - Theile, Albert (Deutsche Blätter), 1943-1946 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 63)
      2 letters from, 2 letters to; Ms. by R.C.B. "Deutschlands Groesste Stunde". Typescript cc. 6p.
    - Time, 1941-1966 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 64)
      11 letters from, 12 letters to.
    - The Times Literary Supplement (London), 1970 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 65)
    - Tree of Knowledge. Correspondence, 1957 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 66)
      Including letters to and from the National Science Foundation, U. S. Department of Commerce, Department of State. 9 letters.
    - Ungar, Frederick, 1978 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 67)
    - W. W. Norton & Company, Inc., 1966 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 68)
    - Wonderly, Wayne, 1968-1974 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 69)
      25 letters from, 32 letters to.
    - Wonderly, Wayne. Lyrica Germanica reprints, Undated; 10 items, 1 cl (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 70)
    - Zinn, Ernst, 1966 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 71)
    - Zohn, Harry. Correspondence, 1970-1976; 2.3.119 (Box 5 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 72-75)
      64 letters & Ptc. from, 97 letters to, 9 related letters; offprints and cl.
      - Correspondence (with Roy C. Bates), 1970-1974 (Box 5 (2.3.119-Zohn, Harry. Correspondence), Folder 72)
      - Correspondence (with Barbara Bates), 1974-1976 (Box 5 (2.3.119-Zohn, Harry. Correspondence), Folder 73)
        Miscellaneous notes.
      - Correspondence re: Bauchwitz/Bates, 1971-1976 (Box 5 (2.3.119-Zohn, Harry. Correspondence), Folder 74)
      - Reprints and cl. of articles by and about Zohn, ca. 12 items (Box 5 (2.3.119-Zohn, Harry. Correspondence), Folder 75)
  - Correspondence regarding Schizophrenia, Psychedelics, Mental Health Issues, 1956-1974; 2.4; 27 file folders
    This sub-series of correspondence (212 letters) centers around issues on the use and legality of psychedelic drugs in the 1960s, as well as correspondence and materials dealing with mental health topics, in particular schizophrenia. Bates' interest in the psychedelic movement of the 1960s led to his participation in the M.I.T.-based Neurobiological and Psychedelic Study Group (1965-1969). Notable among the correspondents are: Kahlil Samra (American Schizophrenia Association), Lisa Biebermann, Abram Hoffer, Peter H. John (Psychedelic Review), Timothy Leary (3 L.), Ralph Metzner, Max Rinkel. Also included in this sub-series are numerous clippings, offprints and brochures relating to individual correspondents.
    - American Schizophrenia Association (Kahlil Samra, Executive Director), 1965-1970 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 76)
      31 letters from, 20 letters to, 6 related letters; record of a telephone conversation between R.C.B. and Kahlil Samra; materials.
    - Barrigar, Robert H., 1964 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 77)
    - Biebermann, Lisa, 1963-1966 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 78)
      5 letters from, 2 letters to; Cl. and articles concerning Lisa Bieberman. 6 items.
    - Blaine, Tom R. (Judge), 1969 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 79)
    - Clark, Walter Houston, 1967 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 80)
      1 letter to; reprint; text of speech.
    - Gordon, Rosemary, 1967 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 81)
    - Hartman, Robert S., 1957 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 1)
      1 letter to, 1 related letter; copies of 2 articles by Hartman.
    - Hitchcock, William Melton, 1965 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 2)
    - Hoffer, Abram (founder, Schizophrenics Anonymous), 1965-1972 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 3)
      14 letters from, 11 letters to; 4 reprints.
    - The Huxley Institute for Biosocial Research (formerly American Schizophrenia Association), 1972-1974 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 4)
      4 letters from, 2 letters concerning; 4 reprints.
    - John, Peter H. (The Psychedelic Review, The International Federation for Internal Freedom), 1963-1965 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 5)
      15 letters from, 22 letters to.
    - International Federation for Internal Freedom, Undated; ca. 20 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 6)
      Memoranda, newsletters, etc.
    - Kleps, Arthur (Neo-American Church), 1966 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 7)
      2 letters from, 2 letters to; 1 cl.; copy of Kleps' "Statement before the Special Senate Judiciary Subcommittee on Narcotics".
    - Kothuys, Anton, 1965 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 8)
    - Leary, Timothy, 1963 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 9)
      1 letter from, 2 letters to; 12 cl. or other materials pertaining to Leary and the Castalia Foundation, Millbrook, NY; copy of Leary's "The Religious Experience: Its Production and Interpretation". 17p.
    - Metzner, Ralph (Castalia Foundation), 1964-1965 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 10)
      3 letters from, 4 letters to; brochure.
    - Moller, Herbert, 1965 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 11)
    - Morrow, Felix (University Books, Inc), 1965 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 12)
      4 letters from, 1 letter to.
    - Neurobiological and Psychedelic Study Group (M.I.T., formerly Psychedelic Research and Study Group), 1965-1969 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 13)
      Form letters, announcements. 12 items.
    - The Psychedelic Review, 1963-1965 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 14)
      4 letters from, 9 letters to.
    - Rinkel, Max, 1965 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 15)
      2 letters from, 3 letters to; notes; 1 cl.; copy of paper delivered by Max Rinkel, "Storm Over 'No Man's Land'. Problems Connected with the Use, Mis-Use, and Abuse of LSD in the United States". 19p.
    - Roberts, Alan H., 1963 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 16)
      1 letter from, 2 letters to; 1 reprint.
    - Schizophrenia (Newsletter of the American Schizophrenia Association/Foundation). Correspondence, 1970 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 17)
      6 items; Schizophrenia, 15 issues 1966-1971; 4 pamphlets.
    - The Student Association for the Study of Hallucinogens (James Gamage, Director), 1968 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 18)
    - Underwood, Richard, 1966 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 19)
      1 letter from, 1 letter to; mimeo. copy of "A Psychedelic Experiment and Experience". 12p.
    - Weil, Gunther M., 1965 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1941-1974; 2.5; 117 file folders
    Included in this section are correspondences (ca. 580 letters) relating to Bates' employment efforts, correspondences with members of the German Consulate, as well as routine correspondence concerning household matters, vacation plans, medical matters and retirement.
    - American Committee for Cultural Freedom / Congress for Cultural Freedom. Correspondence, 1952-1959 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 21)
      9 letters from, 2 letters to; 1 cl.
    - Newsletters, bulletins and brochures distributed by the American Committee for Cultural Freedom, 1951-1956; 15 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 22)
    - Angelson, Blanche, 1941 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 23)
    - The Answer Man (WNBC), 1951 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 24)
    - Artes Gráficas Soler (Manuel Soler), 1975 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 25)
      4 letters from, 3 letters to.
    - Birkmayer, Walter, 1970 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 26)
    - Blake, Walter E. Invitation, 1954 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 27)
    - C. A. Starke Verlag (Hans Kretschmer), 1968 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 28)
    - Caleb, Else, 1945 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 29)
      1 postcard from.
    - Cantor, William, 1970 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 30)
    - The Catholic Committee for Refugees, 1941; 1943 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 31)
    - Chartrand, Gertrude (Mrs. Stanley R), 1951 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 32)
    - Cole, Edwin M., M.D., 1961 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 33)
    - Condolence and miscellaneous cards, letters to Barbara Bates, 1974+ (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 34)
      14 items.
    - Convertible bonds, 1967; 7 items (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 35)
      Materials on convertible bonds; cl.; notes.
    - Crespi, Pachita (Crespi Galleries), 1954 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 36)
    - DeCelle, Denise, 1966; 1990 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 37)
    - DeMarrais, Mary, 1962; 1966; 1974 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 38)
    - Dianetic Research Foundation, Inc., 1951 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 39)
    - Ebbinghaus, Prof. Julius, 1950 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 40)
      1 letter from, 3 letters to; 1 cl.
    - Ehrmann, Henry (Office of War Information), 1943-1944 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 41)
    - Employment correspondence and related materials, Undated; 2.5.22 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 42-53)
      - General correspondence, 1940-1962 (Box 6 (2.5.22-Employment correspondence and related materials), Folder 42)
        Including reference letters, letters to employment agencies. 7 items; application forms; lists of employment opportunities, agencies.
      - Library of Congress, 1942 (Box 6 (2.5.22-Employment correspondence and related materials), Folder 43)
      - American Library Association (Hazel Timmermann), 1942 (Box 6 (2.5.22-Employment correspondence and related materials), Folder 44)
        2 letters from, 1 letter to, accompanied by text of "How American Librarians Can Help Win the Peace", and resumé.
      - Naval Intelligence, 1944 (Box 6 (2.5.22-Employment correspondence and related materials), Folder 45)
      - Thompson J. Walter Co., 1946 (Box 6 (2.5.22-Employment correspondence and related materials), Folder 46)
      - United Nations, 1947-1950 (Box 6 (2.5.22-Employment correspondence and related materials), Folder 47)
        1 letter from, 3 letters to; record of an interview; curriculum vita.
      - Crowell-Collier Publishing Co., 1947 (Box 6 (2.5.22-Employment correspondence and related materials), Folder 48)
      - Young B. Smith, 1948 (Box 6 (2.5.22-Employment correspondence and related materials), Folder 49)
        1 letter from, 1 letter to; manuscript by R.C.B. "Political Psychology and 'Ecology' of Legislations". Draft. 4p.; 1 cl.
      - Voice of America (including Dept. of State), 1948-1951 (Box 6 (2.5.22-Employment correspondence and related materials), Folder 50)
        3 letters from, 1 letter to; notes and ideas. 12p.; 3 cl.
      - U.S. Government Civil Service. Application forms, civil service test appointments, 1951- 1952 (Box 6 (2.5.22-Employment correspondence and related materials), Folder 51)
      - Investors Diversified Services, Inc. (IDS), 1951-1952 (Box 6 (2.5.22-Employment correspondence and related materials), Folder 52)
        2 letters from, 2 letters to; record of an interview; notes and materials.
      - Peace Corps, 1962 (Box 6 (2.5.22-Employment correspondence and related materials), Folder 53)
        1 letter from, 1 letter to; informational materials.
    - England, Glyn, 1966 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 54)
    - Fasch, Clifford (Fasch Studios), 1966 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 55)
    - Felton, Happy, 1951 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 56)
    - Flesch, Philipp, Undated (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 57)
      1 letter from; Ms. of poem.
    - Foster-Harris, Prof, 1959 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 58)
    - Freeman, Harrop A., 1952 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 59)
    - Frey, Mitsue, 1975-1976 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 60)
    - German Consul General correspondence, 1959-1974; 2.5.30 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 61-69)
      - General correspondence, 1959-1974 (Box 6 (2.5.30-German Consul General correspondence), Folder 61)
        9 letters from, 9 letters to.
      - Federer, Georg A., 1959-1963 (Box 6 (2.5.30-German Consul General correspondence), Folder 62)
        3 letters from, 6 letters to.
      - Keudell, Wilhelm von, 1966-1970 (Box 6 (2.5.30-German Consul General correspondence), Folder 63)
        6 letters, cards from, 2 letters to.
      - Kurbjuhn, Paul, 1969-1970 (Box 6 (2.5.30-German Consul General correspondence), Folder 64)
      - Linhart, Hubert, 1966-1967 (Box 6 (2.5.30-German Consul General correspondence), Folder 65)
        1 letter, 2 cards from, 1 letter to.
      - Sante, Hans-Heinrich, 1969-1971 (Box 6 (2.5.30-German Consul General correspondence), Folder 66)
        5 cards from.
      - Schmidt-Pauli, Edgar von, 1965-1971 (Box 6 (2.5.30-German Consul General correspondence), Folder 67)
        12 letters from, 8 letters to; 4 cl.
      - Schmidt-Schlegel, Philipp, 1961-1965 (Box 6 (2.5.30-German Consul General correspondence), Folder 68)
        13 letters, cards from, 7 letters to; 2 cl.
      - Weber, Gerhart, 1964-1966 (Box 6 (2.5.30-German Consul General correspondence), Folder 69)
        3 cards from, 2 letters to.
    - German Information Center (Rüdiger von Wechmar, Director), 1969 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 70)
    - Germanic Notes (Lawrence Thompson), 1974 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 71)
    - Godfrey, Arthur, 1967-1968 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 72)
    - Goethe House, 1957-1970 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 73)
    - Goldman, Eric, 1966 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 74)
    - Goldstein, Beverly and Irwin, 1974 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 75)
    - Greene, Janey, 1946 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 76)
    - Greenough, Peter B., 1965-1966 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 77)
    - Guillemin, Roger, 1970 (Box 6 (2-Correspondence Files), Folder 78)